{
    "id": "feee0fd25d5045e58c916e3744032858",
    "title": "Identify The Adjectives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "fda80d9d85934ad88bfe8be55388898d",
            "title": "Identify The Adjective",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The cake baking in the oven made the whole house fragrant.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun house.",
                    "answers": [
                        "cake",
                        "oven",
                        "fragrant"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The climber dangled in midair, held by a frail rope.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun rope.",
                    "answers": [
                        "dangled",
                        "midair",
                        "frail"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was a lot of frantic activity just before the arrival of royal visitors.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun activity.",
                    "answers": [
                        "lot",
                        "before",
                        "frantic"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was always a lot of fraternal affection between the boys.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun affection.",
                    "answers": [
                        "always",
                        "fraternal",
                        "between"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The puppy flopped around on the slippery floor.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun floor.",
                    "answers": [
                        "puppy",
                        "around",
                        "slippery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The wallpaper had a floral pattern.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun pattern.",
                    "answers": [
                        "wallpaper",
                        "floral",
                        "pattern"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The shop sells ice-cream in eight different flavors.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shop",
                        "eight",
                        "different"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Lack of civilian clothes was the one flaw in our escape plan.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "civilian",
                        "one",
                        "escape",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "The hot coals made a fizzle as they hit the water.",
                    "description": "It modifies the noun coals.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hot",
                        "fizzle",
                        "water"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That was a flagrant abuse of his authority.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "flagrant",
                        "authority"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This new medication fills an urgent need.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "medication",
                        "new",
                        "urgent",
                        "need"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our final meeting for the season is next Wednesday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "final",
                        "season",
                        "next"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}